theagencyone.com 2011-06-14

# Privacy Policy

Updated: April 20, 2009

Your privacy is important to us, so we have created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our web sites and when we serve advertisements on our network of websites, why we collect it and how it is used.

Please read this privacy policy carefully since by visiting this site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our website Terms and Conditions.

During your visit to the Site, we and/or our third party vendors may collect certain information, as follows.  

## Personally Identifiable Information

We do not collect "Personally Identifiable Information" or"PII" on any of our websites.  PII means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including first and last name, physical address, email address, or telephone number.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We automatically receive and record anonymous information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website. We use log files to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us. This information may be stored on our systems for about one year. We use technology, including technology from its third party advertising vendors, which includes cookies, "web beacons" and/or "action tags." A "cookie" is a small text file stored by your browser on your computer when you visit our Network. A "web beacon" or "action tag" is a small image (usually 1x1 pixel) embedded in a web page or email. We use cookies, web beacons and action tags to collect non-personally identifiable data to provide better and more relevant services and messages to that user. Cookies, web beacons and action tags permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information.

As a rule, non-personally identifiable information is anonymous and is not used to identify a specific person.

Web surfers may elect not to provide non-personally identifiable information by following the cookie opt-out procedures set forth below.

## Personally identifiable information

We do not collect PII.

## Non-personally identifiable information

We may use your non-personal information in order to better target advertisements, to provide aggregate reporting to advertisers and clients, and to improve our advertising systems and products. We use the information to analyze site usage, administer the site, understand usage and navigation trends in aggregate, and determine the relevance of content.  We may also share non-personally identifiable information with our subsidiaries and third party partners for similar use. 

We do not collect PII.

We employ commercially reasonable security measures to ensure the security of all data. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

## Non-personally identifiable information

Our advertising partners may be members of the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and work with industry leading companies to address important privacy and consumer protection issues in online advertising.

If you prefer not to receive behavioral ads you may opt-out of this anonymous ad targeting. Please note that if you opt-out ad companies may continue to collect non-personal information in connection with ad serving for limited reporting and auditing purposes. Examples of these include but are not limited to reporting overall advertising performance, geographic activity, and other similar analyses.  Most browsers will accept cookies unless you change your browser settings to refuse them and opt-out of the use of cookies and those of our third party advertising technology vendors. For more information on cookies and how to manage and delete them, please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

We are very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and make every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Our website, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children under 13. For that reason, we does not knowingly collect or maintain information on the websites from persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access the websites at any time or in any manner.

We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.  For all other changes, it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. Your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.
